kcet.org 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy | KCET

Effective Date: December 2, 2014

KCETLink (" **KCETLink** " or " **we** ," " **our** " or " **us** ") welcomes its members, donors, viewers, and visitors to the KCETLink's websites (located at www.kcet.org/.com/.net; aplaceofourown.org/.net/.tv; placeofourown.org/.net/.tv; losninosensucasa.org/.com/.net/.tv; www.kcetlink.org; viewchange.org; standupplanet.org; and www.linktv.org) and any of our other online services where this Privacy Policy is posted (collectively, the " **KCETLink Sites** " and each referred to as a " **Site** "). This " **Privacy Policy** " governs your use of the KCETLink Sites (including, without limitation, both mobile and online versions of our KCETLink Sites), and also applies to your use of all features, applications, content, downloads, widgets, and other services that we make available through the KCETLink Sites and/or that post a link to this Privacy Policy, regardless of how you access or use them, whether via personal computers, mobile devices, or otherwise. This Privacy Policy does not apply to our data collection activities offline or otherwise outside of the KCETLink Sites (unless otherwise stated below), and does not govern the data practices of third parties that may collect information in connection with the KCETLink Sites.

By participating in the KCETLink activities described below and/or using the KCETLink Sites, you consent to the terms set forth in this Privacy Policy and our collection, use and sharing of your information and data, and other activities, as described below, and agree to the [Terms of Use](https://www.linktv.org/terms-of-use), and, should you participate in an Online Forum (described below) the rules (if any) set forth in Online Forums.

**To the extent we provide you notice on our KCETLink Sites of different or additional privacy policies or practices (e.g., at the point of our collection), those additional terms shall govern such data collection and use.**

**_Linkable Table of Contents_**

**It is important that you read and understand the entire Privacy Policy before using the Site. To ease your review of the Privacy Policy, each section below has a brief introductory summary plus a link to the full explanation. Click on the headings or the "More" buttons to be taken to the full explanation. Any capitalized terms are defined in the introduction or elsewhere in the Privacy Policy.**

**1\. What Information Does the Site Collect?**

  1. **Information You Provide to Us**

We may collect certain Personal Information (defined below) and Demographic Information (defined below) that you provide when you interact with the Site. For example, we may collect this information through various forms and in various places on the Site, including when you purchase a membership or when you otherwise interact with the Site. More

  2. **Information We Collect and Store As You Access and Use the Site**

Certain information may be collected from you automatically when you access and use the Site. For example, we and third parties may use Tracking Technologies (defined below) to collect Usage Information (defined below) based on your Device Identifier (defined below) for a variety of purposes, including tracking, targeting, and advertising, which may include activities across time and third party locations. More

  3. **Information Third Parties Provide About You**

We may obtain information about you from third parties. More

  4. **Interactions with Third Party Sites**

If you interact with third party sites, those sites may send us information about you, and you or we may send them information about you. More

  5. **Information You Provide About a Third Party**

You may give us information about others, such as when you send a friend a message. More

  6. **California "Do Not Track" Disclosures**

We do not look for or respond to "do not track" signals, but you may have certain other options regarding tracking and/or targeting. More  

**2\. How Do We Use the Information Collected?**

  1. **Use of Information By Us**

We use your Personal Information (defined below), Demographic Information (defined below) and Usage Information (defined below) for a variety of purposes detailed in this section. More

  2. **Use of Information for Recruitment Purposes**

If you apply for a job with us, we use the application information you provide and information we receive from other sources for considering you for a position. More

**3\. How and When We Share Information with Third Parties?**

We may provide your information to third parties under various circumstances. These may include:

  1. **When You Request Information From or Provide Information to Third Parties**

If you request information from third parties, request that we send information to third parties, or interact with third party sites, content, ads, or tools (including Facebook and other third party share functionality), we may share your information with such parties and/or they may collect your information directly. This may also include ordering or purchasing products from third parties through us where we indicate that the third party rather than us is the seller. More

  2. **Third Parties Providing Services on our Behalf**

Our vendors may collect your information, share with us your information, or we may share your information with them. More

  3. **Administrative and Legal Reasons**

There are a variety of administrative and legal reasons for which we may share some or all of your information.More

  4. **Affiliates and Business Transfer**

We may share your information with our affiliates, and in the event of a sale, merger, or similar transaction.More

  5. **Co-branded Areas**

Co-branded areas may include information collection by us and third parties. Such third parties privacy policies, not ours, govern their practices. More

  6. **Auctions, Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions**

To enter a Promotion, you may be required to consent to certain information sharing. More

  7. **Your California Privacy Rights**

Californian residents may request information about sharing of certain personal information with third parties for the third parties' direct marketing purposes by contacting us using the methods described in this section.More

**4\. What About Information I Disclose Publicly?**

  1. **Online Forums**

The Site offers Online Forums (defined below). All content you submit to an Online Forum is public (i.e., available for anyone to see). Use caution when participating in any Online Forum, as any information you post on an Online Forum can be collected and used by third parties and may result in your receiving unsolicited communications from third parties. More

  2. **User-Generated Content**

This Privacy Policy does not apply to content you choose to post or share publicly on the Site such as the content that you post in an Online Forum. More

  3. **Name and Likeness**

You may grant us the right to use your name and/or likeness in connection with your User Content and activities in Online Forums. More

**5\. Ads and Information About You**

We may serve you targeted ads on the Site based on your location, information, and/or behavior. If you object, you can exercise choices some third parties offer. More

**6\. Do Third-Party Content, Links to Third-Party Sites and/or Third-Party Apps Appear on the Site?**

We may allow you to access third-party content on the Site, or to link to third-party applications and locations from the Site, but we are not responsible for your interaction with third-party content, apps, and locations. More

**7\. How Do I Change My Information and Communications Preferences?**

You may change certain account information and preferences. More

**8\. What About Transfer of Information to the United States?**

You consent to your data being transferred to the United States, which has different data protection laws than other countries. More

**9\. What Should Parents Know About Children?**

We do not intend to collect Personal Information (defined below) from children. If you think we have, let us know.More

**10\. What About Security?**

No data security is absolute, but we take reasonable steps to secure data appropriately. More

**11\. What About Changes to the Privacy Policy?**

We may change this Privacy Policy upon posting of a revised policy. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy and your use of our Site indicates your consent to the Privacy Policy posted at the time of use. However, we will not use your previously collected Personal Information in a manner materially different than represented at the time it was collected without your consent. More

**_The Full Detailed Privacy Policy_**

**1\. What Information Does the Site Collect?**

We may use various methods and technologies to collect and/or store Usage Information (" **Tracking Technologies** "). Tracking Technologies may set, change, alter, or modify settings or configurations on your Device. A few of the Tracking Technologies include, without limitation, the following (and subsequent technology and methods later developed):

We may use Tracking Technologies for a variety of purposes, including:

**_Strictly Necessary._**  We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that we consider are strictly necessary to allow you to use and access our Site, including cookies required to prevent fraudulent activity, improve security, or allow you to make use of Site functionality.

**_Performance-Related._**  We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are useful in order to assess the performance of the Site, including as part of our analytic practices or otherwise to improve the content, products, or services offered through the Site.

**_Functionality-Related._**  We may use cookies or other Tracking Technologies that are required to offer you enhanced functionality when accessing the Site, including identifying you when you visit our Site or keeping track of your specified preferences, including in terms of the presentation of content on our Site.

**_Targeting-Related._**  We may use Tracking Technologies to deliver content relevant to your interests on our Service and third-party services based on how you interact with our content. This includes Tracking Technologies to understand the usefulness to you of the content that has been delivered to you.

There may be other Tracking Technologies now and later devised and used by us in connection with the Site. Further, third parties may use Tracking Technologies in connection with our Site, which may include the collection of information about your online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services. We may not control those Tracking Technologies and we are not responsible for them. However, you consent to potentially encountering third-party Tracking Technologies in connection with use of our Site and accept that our statements under this Privacy Policy do not apply to the Tracking Technologies or practices of such third parties.

  1. **Information You Provide to Us**

On the Site, we may ask you to provide certain categories of information such as: (1) personality identifiable information, which is information that identifies you personally, such as your first and last name, email address, home address, date of birth, and phone number (" **Personal Information** "); and (2) demographic information, such as information about your gender (" **Demographic Information** "). KCETLink may collect Personal Information and Demographic Information through various forms and in various places on the Site, including through its membership subscriptions, pledges of financial support, and/or services which require subscriptions such as an email or postal newsletter (" **Subscription Activities** "). On occasion, we may hold certain auctions, contests, sweepstakes, or other promotional events (collectively, " **Promotions** ") and, in connection with those Promotions, we may request that partcipants provide Personal Information. We may also collect Personal Information and Demographic Information through various forms and in various places on the Site, including if you sign-up for a membership, through "contact us" forms, or when you otherwise interact with the KCETLink Sites. If we combine Demographic Information with the Personal Information we collect directly from you on the Site, we will treat the combined data as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy.

  2. **Information We Collect and Store As You Access and Use the Site**

In addition to any Personal Information or other information that you choose to submit to us via our Site, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies that automatically (or passively) store or collect certain information whenever you visit or interact with the Site (" **Usage Information** "). This Usage Information may be stored or accessed using a variety of technologies that may be downloaded to your personal computer, browser, laptop, tablet, mobile phone, or other device (a " **Device** ") whenever you visit or interact with our Site. Like all web services, the web server(s) of KCETLink Sites automatically create log files for each visitor who accesses the KCETLink Sites. These "access logs" allow us to make the KCETLink Sites more useful to our visitors. The access logs do NOT record a visitor's name, address, phone number or credit card numbers. Rather, they contain some or all of the following Usage Information:

We may use various methods and technologies to collect and/or store Usage Information (" **Tracking Technologies** "). Tracking Technologies may set, change, alter, or modify settings or configurations on your Device. A few of the Tracking Technologies include, without limitation, the following (and subsequent technology and methods later developed):

    * Your IP address, UDID or other unique identifier ("Device Identifier"). A Device Identifier is a number that is automatically assigned to your Device used to access the Site, and our computers identify your Device by its Device Identifier;
    * Your Device functionality (including browser, operating system, hardware, mobile network information);
    * The URL that referred you to our Site;
    * The areas within our Site that you visit and your activities there, including remembering you and your preferences;
    * Your Device location;
    * Your Device characteristics; and
    * Certain other Device data, including the time of day, among other information.
    * **_Cookies._**  A cookie is a data file placed on a Device when it is used to visit the Site. A Flash cookie (or locally shared object) is a data file placed on a Device via the Adobe Flash plug-in that may be built-in to or downloaded by you to your Device. HTML5 cookies can be programmed through HTML5 local storage. Unlike Flash cookies, HTML5 cookies do not require a plug-in. Regular cookies may generally be disabled or removed by tools that are available as part of most commercial browsers, and in some but not all instances can be blocked in the future by selecting certain settings. Each browser you use will need to be set separately and different browsers offer different functionality and options in this regard. Also, these tools may not be effective with regard to Flash cookies or HTML5 cookies. For information on disabling Flash cookies go to Adobe's web site [www.adobe.com](http://www.adobe.com/). Please be aware that if you disable or remove cookies, Flash cookies, or HTML5 cookies on your Device, some parts of our Site may not function properly, and that when you revisit our Site your ability to limit cookies is subject to your browser settings and limitations.
    * **_Web Beacons._**  Small graphic images or other web programming code called "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 GIFs" or "clear GIFs") may be included in our Site's pages and messages. Web beacons may be inviisble to you, but any electronic image or other web programming code inserted into a page or e-mail can act as a web beacon. Web beacons or similar technologies may be used for a number of purposes, including, without limitation, to count visitors to the Site, to monitor how users navigate the Site, to count how many e-mails that were sent were actually opened or to count how many particular or links were actually viewed.
    * **_Embedded Scripts._** An embedded script is programming code that is designed to collect information about your interactions with the Site, such as the links you click on. The code is temporarily downloaded onto your Device from our web server or a third party service provider, is active only while you are connected to the Site, and is deactivated or deleted thereafter.
    * **_Browser Fingerprinting._** Collection and analysis of information from your Device, such as, without limitation, your operating system, plug-ins, system fonts and other data, for purposes of identification.
    * **_Recognition Technologies._** Technologies, including application of statistical probability to data sets, which attempt to recognize or make assumptions about users and devices (e.g., that a user of multiple devices is the same user).
    * **_ETag, or entity tag._** A feature of the cache in browsers. It is an opaque identifier assigned by a web server to a specific version of a resource found at a URL. If the resource content at that URL ever changes, a new and different ETag is assigned. Used in this manner ETags are a form of Device Identifier. ETag tracking may generate unique tracking values even where the consumer blocks HTTP, Flash and/or HTML5 cookies.

  3. **Information Third Parties Provide About You**

We may receive information about you from friends and others that use the Site, such as when they submit content to us or post on the Site. Additionally, we may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect directly from you on our Site with outside records from third parties for various purposes, including to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and to offer you opportunities that may be of interest to you. For example, KCETLink may exchange with, or rent to/from, a range of organizations the names and mailing addresses of individuals provided that the organizations agreed in writing to use KCETLink provided Personal Information for the sole purpose of mailing individuals information about the organization's products/services and fundraising solicitations; you may instruct KCETLink not to share your Personal Information with such organizations by following the directions listed below under Section 7: "How Do I Change My Information and Communication Preferences?". To the extent we combine information we receive from those sources with Personal Information we collect on the Site, it will be treated as Personal Information and we will apply this Privacy Policy to such combined information, unless we have disclosed otherwise. In no other circumstances do our statements under this Privacy Policy apply to information we receive about you from third parties.

  4. **Interactions with Third Party Sites**

The Site may include functionality that allows certain kinds of interactions between the Site and your account on a third-party web site or application. The use of this functionality may involve the third-party operator providing certain information, including Personal Information, to us. For example, we may provide third-party sites' interfaces or links on the Site to facilitate your sending a communication from the Site. For example, we may use third parties to facilitate emails, Tweets or Facebook postings. These third parties may retain any information used or provided in any such communications or other activities and these third parties' practices are not subject to our Privacy Policy. KCETLink may not control or have access to your communications through these third parties. Further, when you use third-party sites or services, you are using their services and not our services and they, not we, are responsible for their practices. You should review the applicable third-party privacy policies before using such third-party tools on our Site.

  5. **Information You Provide About a Third Party**

You may send someone else a communication from the Site, such as sending an invitation to a friend. If so, the information you provide (names, email addresses, mobile number, etc.) is used to facilitate the communication and is not used by us for any other marketing purpose unless we obtain consent from that person or we explicitly say otherwise. Please be aware that when you use any send-to-a-friend functionality on our Site, your email address, mobile number, name, or user name and message may be included in the communication sent to your addressee(s).

    1. **California "Do Not Track" Disclosures**

Various third parties are developing or have developed signals or other mechanisms for the expression of consumer choice regarding the collection of information about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across third-party web sites or online services (e.g., browser "do not track" signals). Currently, we do not monitor or take any action with respect to these signals or other mechanisms.​  

    2.  How Do We Use the Information Collected?

  6. **Use of Information By Us.**  KCETLink may use your Personal Information, Demographic Information, or Usage Information for various purposes, including:   

    * to process transactions (such as donations) or provide you with information such as to send you electronic newsletters, emails or to provide you with special offers or promotional and marketing materials on behalf of us or third parties, including to let you know about new products, services or upcoming events;

    * to enable you to participate in a variety of the Site's features such as to enable you to participate in online auctions, sweepstakes, contests, or other promotions;

    * to provide you with information as part of your membership or participation in a subscription based service provided by KCETLink;

    * to improve the Site, marketing endeavours or our Site offerings;

    * to customize your experience on the Site or to serve you specific content or ads that are relevant to you;

    * to respond to your requests for information such as to provide customer support;

    * to contact you with regard to your use of the Site, such as to request that you participate in a survey, and, in our discretion, changes to the Site and/or Site's policies;

    * to notify you of product recalls or providing other information concerning products you have purchased;

    * for informational notices about KCETLink or KCETLink member stations;

    * to identify your product and Site preferences so that you can be informed of new or additional products, services. and promotions;

    * for internal business purposes; and

    * for purposes disclosed in our [Terms of Use](https://www.linktv.org/about/terms-of-use) or otherwise at the time you provide your information or as otherwise set forth in this Privacy Policy.

  7. **Use of Information for Recruitment Purposes**

Where you have provided us with information as part of an online application for employment or internship, we may use that information in order to allow us to make an informed decision about whether to proceed with your application. We may, as part of this recruitment process, collect information about your education, employment history and similar matters and verify your information is accurate in consultation with third parties. Where this information is considered to be sensitive, you expressly consent to our processing of this information for recruitment purposes only by submitting it to us.

**3.  How and When We Share Information with Third Parties?**

We may share non-Personal Information, such as aggregated user statistics, with third parties. Further, we may share your Personal Information with third parties such as our co-promotional and business partners or others with whom we have marketing or other relationships for the third parties' direct marketing purposes. If you are a California resident, you have the right to request additional information about this sharing, so please see Section (3)(g) below. We may share your Device Identifiers with third parties along with data related to you and your activities. In addition, we may share the information we have collected about you, including Personal Information, as disclosed at the time you provide your information and as described below or otherwise in this Privacy Policy. KCETLink may disclose your information as follows:

  1. **When You Request Information From or Provide Information to Third Parties**

You may be presented with an option on our Site to receive certain information and/or marketing offers directly from third parties or to have us send certain information to third parties or give them access to it. If you choose to do so, your Personal Information and other information may be disclosed to such third parties and all information you disclose will be subject to the third party privacy policies and practices of such third parties. In addition, third parties may store, collect or otherwise have access to your information when you interact with their Tracking Technologies, content, tools apps or ads on our Site or link to them from our Site. This may include using third party tools such as Facebook, Twitter, Pinterest or other third party posting or content sharing tools. It may also include ordering or purchasing products from third parties through us where we indicate that the third party rather than us is the seller. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of such third parties and, therefore, you should review such third party privacy policies and practices of such third parties prior to requesting information from or otherwise interacting with them.

  2. **Third Parties Providing Services on our Behalf**

We may use third-party vendors to perform certain services on behalf of us or the Site, such as hosting the Site and processing credit cards, designing and/or operating the Site's features, tracking the Site's activities and analytics, and enabling us to send you special offers or perform other administrative services. We may provide these vendors with access to user information, including Device Identifiers and Personal Information, to carry out the services they are performing for you or for us. Third-party analytics and other service providers may set and access their own Tracking Technologies on your Device and they may otherwise collect or have access to information about you, potentially including Personal Information, about you. We are not responsible for those third party technologies or activities arising out of them. However, some may offer you certain choices regarding their practices and information as to their use of your information; to the extent we have been informed, please click here to learn more of the availability of such choices. We are not responsible for the effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties' opt-out options.

  3. **Administrative and Legal Reasons**

We may access, use, preserve, transfer and disclose your information (including Device Identifiers and Personal Information) to third parties: (i) to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, subpoenas, governmental requests, or legal process if in our good faith opinion such is required or permitted by law; (ii) to protect and/or defend the Site's [Terms of Use](https://www.linktv.org/terms-of-use) or other policies applicable to the Site, including investigation of potential violations thereof; (iii) to protect the safety, rights, property or security of the Site, KCETLink and KCETLink subsidiaries, affiliates, business associates or partners, members, donors, viewers, and website visitors, the public or KCETLink and its employees or any third party; and/or (iv) to detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues. Further, we may use IP addresses or other Device Identifiers, to identify users, and may do so in cooperation with third parties such as copyright owners, internet service providers, wireless service providers, and/or law enforcement agencies, including disclosing such information to third parties, all in our discretion, subject to applicable law. Such disclosures may be carried out without notice to you.

  4. **Affiliates and Business Transfer**

We may share your information, including your Device Identifiers and Personal Information, Demographic Information, and Usage Information with our parent, subsidiaries and affiliates. We also reserve the right to disclose and transfer all such information: (i) to a subsequent owner, co-owner or operator of the Site or applicable database; or (ii) in connection with a merger, consolidation, restructuring, the sale of substantially all of our interests, and/or assets or other corporate change, including, during the course of any due diligence process.

  5. **Co-branded Areas**

Certain areas of the Site may be provided to you in association with third parties (" **Co-Branded Areas** ") such as our donation partners, and may require you to disclose Personal Information to them. Such Co-Branded Areas will identify the third party and indicate if they have a privacy policy that applies to their collection and use of you information. If you elect to register for products and/or services, communicate with such third parties or download their content or applications, at Co-Branded Areas, you may be providing your information to both us and the third party. Further, if you sign-in to a Co-Branded Area with a username and password obtained on the Site, your Personal Information may be disclosed to the identified third parties for that Co-Branded Area. We are not responsible for such third party's data collection or practices and you should look to such third party privacy policies for more information.

  6. **Auctions, Sweepstakes, Contests and Promotions**

We may offer Promotions through the KCETLink Sites that may require registration. By participating in a Promotion, you are agreeing to the Terms and Conditions or Official Rules (as applicable) that govern that Promotion, which may contain specific requirements of you, including, allowing the sponsor of the Promotion to use your name, voice, and/or likeness in advertising or marketing associated with the Promotion. If a Promotion is offered by or with a sponsoring third party(ies), your participation in such Promotion is your authorization to KCETLink to share your Personal Information with the sponsoring third party(ies). If you do not want your Personal Information to be shared under these circumstances you may choose to not participate. If you choose to enter a Promotion, Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties or the public in connection with the administration of such Promotion, including, without limitation, in connection with winner selection, prize fulfillment, and as required by law or permitted by the Promotion's official rules or terms and conditions, such as on a winners list.

  7. **Your California Privacy Rights**

We may elect to share information about you with third parties for those third parties' direct marketing purposes. California Civil Code § 1798.83 permits California residents who have supplied personal information (as defined in the law) to us to, under certain circumstances, request, and obtain certain information regarding our disclosure, if any, of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. If this law applies to you, you may obtain the categories of personal information shared by us and the names and addresses of all third parties that received personal information for their direct marketing purposes from us during the immediately prior calendar year (e.g., requests made in 2014 will receive information about 2013 sharing activities). To make such a request, please provide sufficient information for us to determine if this applies to you, attest to the fact that you are a California resident and provide a current California address for our response. To make such a request (limit one request per year), please send an email to [legal@kcet.org](mailto:legal@kcet.org), with "California Privacy Rights" as the subject line or mail us a letter to: KCETLink, Attention: Privacy Division, 900 West Alameda Ave., Burbank, California 91505. You must include your full name, email address, and postal address in your request. 

**4.  What About Information I Disclose Publicly?**

  1. **Online Forums**

KCETLink offers online forums on the Site such as blogs, bulletin boards, chat forums and message boards (" **Online Forums** "), which may require participant registration. The nature of Online Forums such as blogging, chat forums and message boards is to share information and ideas with a public audience. Any information you submit for posting on an Online Forum may be posted on the KCETLink Sites or otherwise be made available to the general public. You are advised to use caution when participating in any Online Forum, as any information you post on the Online Forum can be collected and used by third parties and may result in your receiving unsolicited communications from third parties. Users under the age of 18 should be particularly careful not to divulge any Personal Information when using Online Forums. Children under the age of 13 are not permitted to use the Online Forums.

  2. **User-Generated Content**

The Site may permit you to submit ideas, photographs, user profiles, writings, music, video, audio recordings, computer graphics, pictures, data, questions, comments, suggestions, or other content, including Personal Information (collectively, "User Content"). We or others may store, display, reproduce, publish, distribute, or otherwise use User Content online or offline in any media or format (currently existing or hereafter developed) and may or may not attribute it to you. Others may have access to this User Content and may have the ability to share it with third parties. Please think carefully before deciding what information you share, including Personal Information, in connection with your User Content. Please note that we do not control who will have access to the information that you choose to make public, and cannot ensure that parties who have access to such publicly available information will respect your privacy or keep it secure. Our promises under this Privacy Policy do not apply to any information that you disclose publicly, share with others or otherwise upload onto the publicly available portions of our Site. We are not responsible for the accuracy, use or misuse of any User Content that you disclose or receive from third parties through the Site.

  3. **Name and Likeness**

We may also publish your name, voice, likeness, and other Personal Information that is part of your User Content, and we may use the content, or any portion of the content, for advertising, marketing, publicity, and promotional activities. For full terms and conditions regarding User Content you submit to the Site, please review our [Terms of Use](https://www.linktv.org/terms-of-use).

**5.  Ads and Information About You**

We may use third parties such as network advertisers and ad exchanges to serve advertisements on the Site or across the Internet and may use third party analytics service providers to evaluate and provide us and/or third parties with information about the use of these ads on third party sites and viewing of ads and of our content. Network advertisers are third parties that display advertisements, which may be based on your activities across the Internet and mobile media (" **Behavioral Ads** "). Behavioral Ads enable us to target advertisements to you for products and services in which we believe you might be interested. If you object to receiving Behavioral Ads on the Site, you can learn more about your ability to limit Behavioral Ads below. Our third party ad network and exchange providers, the advertisers and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own technologies on your Device and track certain behavioral Usage Information via a Device Identifier. These third party technologies may be set to, among other things: (a) help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) prevent you from seeing the same advertisements; and (c) understand the usefulness of the advertisements that have been delivered to you. You acknowledge and agree that associated technology may access and use your Device and may set or change settings on your Device in connection with the associated operations. Note that any images (or any other parts of content) served by third parties in association with third-party ads or other content may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities.

Statements regarding our practices do not apply to the methods for collecting information used by these third parties or the use of the information that such third parties collect. We do however work with third parties to make efforts to have you provided with information on their practices and any available opportunity to exercise choice. The relevant third party's terms of service, privacy policy, permissions, notices, and choices should be reviewed regarding their collection, storage and sharing practices. We make no representations regarding the policies or practices of third party advertisers or advertising networks or exchanges or related third parties.

Some third parties may offer you certain choices regarding their practices, and information we have been informed of regarding such choices is available here. Further, while sites use a variety of companies to serve advertisements, you may wish to visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/optout_nonppii.asp>, which provides information regarding this practice by Network Advertising Initiative (" **NAI** ") members, and your choices regarding having this information used by these companies, including the "opt-out" procedures of NAI members. Opting out of one or more NAI members only means that those NAI members no longer will be allowed under their own rules to deliver Behavioral Ads to you, but does not mean you will no longer receive any targeted content and/or ads. Also, if your browsers are configured to reject cookies when you visit this opt-out page, or you subsequently erase your cookies, use a different Device or change web browsers, your NAI opt-out may not, or may no longer, be effective. You may also opt-out of receiving Behavioral Ads on participating sites and services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance (" **DAA** ") website at <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/#completed>. Similar limitations may apply to the DAA opt-out. We are not responsible for effectiveness of or compliance with any third parties' opt-out options or programs.

**6.  Do Third-Party Content, Links to Third-Party Sites and/or Third-Party Apps Appear on the Site?**

The Site may contain content that is supplied by a third party, and those third parties may collect Usage Information and your Device Identifier when pages from the Site are served to you. In addition, when you are on the Site you may be directed to other sites that are operated and controlled by third parties that we do not control. We are not responsible for the data collection and privacy practices employed by any of these third parties or their services and they may be tracking you across multiple sites and may be sharing the results of that tracking with us and/or others. For example, if you "click" on a link, the "click" may take you off the Site onto a different site. These other sites may associate their Tracking Technologies with you, independently collect data about you, including Personal Information, and may or may not have their own published privacy policies.

Third-party applications may also be available via the Site. The owners of these applications (" **Third-Party Owners** ") may collect Personal Information and other data from you and may have their own policies and practices. We are not responsible for how Third-Party Owners or their applications collect or use your information and they may be tracking you across multiple sites and may be sharing the results of that tracking with us and/or others. These Third-Party Owners may have their own terms of service, privacy policies or other policies and ask you to agree to the same. We are not responsible for these third-party privacy policies or the practices of Third-Party Owners. Be sure to review any available policies before submitting any personally identifiable information to a third-party application or otherwise interacting with it and exercise caution in connection with these applications. We also encourage you to note when you leave our Site and to review the third-party privacy policies of all third-party locations and exercise caution in connection with them.

As KCETLink strives to maintain the integrity and quality of the KCETLink Sites, you are invited to send your feedback regarding the sites connected through a link on the KCETLink Sites (including if a link does not work) by sending an email to [viewerservices@kcet.org](mailto:viewerservices@kcet.org).

**7.  How Do I Change My Information and Communications Preferences?**

If at any time you need to update your Personal Information with KCETLink, notify us of your preference ("opt-out" versus "opt-in"), change your preference as to receipt of KCETLink newsletters and promotional materials or our sharing of your Personal Information with third parties, or if you just have a question, comment or concern about how KCETLink uses your Personal Information, simply contact us in writing as follows:

Email: [legal@kcet.org](mailto:legal@kcet.org)  
Post: KCETLink  
Attention: Privacy Division  
2900 West Alameda Ave.  
Burbank, California 91505

Please note that "opting out" may adversely impact your ability to participate in Subscription Activities, Promotions, and the Online Forums, as well as prevent us from responding or processing your request for information, products, or services.

We welcome all other questions, comments, and concerns you may have about KCETLink and the Website:  
Email: [viewerservices@kcet.org](mailto:viewerservices@kcet.org)  
U.S. Mail:  
KCETLink 

2900 West Alameda Ave. 

Burbank, California 91505 

Attn: Member Services 

Phone: (747) 201-KCET (5238) 

You are responsible for maintaining the accuracy of the information you submit to us, such as your contact information provided as part of registration. If you send us an email to update your information, please include "Change of Information" in the subject line of your email. If so, we will make good faith efforts to make requested changes in our then active databases as soon as reasonably practicable. Please note that it is not always possible to remove or delete completely all of your information from our databases and that residual data may remain on backup media or for other reasons. Also, if you have made any public postings on the Site such as in forums or blogs, these communications cannot generally be removed. When you edit your Personal Information or change your preferences on the Site, information that you remove may persist internally for our administrative purposes. You may cancel or modify our email marketing communications you receive from us by following the instructions contained within our promotional emails or in some cases by logging into your Site account and changing your communication preferences. This will not affect subsequent subscriptions and if your opt-out is limited to certain types of emails the opt-out will be so limited. Subsequent or different subscriptions will be unaffected. Please note that we reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to your account or use of our Site, such as administrative and Site announcements and these transactional account messages may be unaffected if you choose to opt-out from receiving our marketing communications.

* _8.  *What About Transfer of Information to the United States?_

Our Site is operated in the United States and intended for users located in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be aware that information we collect, including Personal Information, will be transferred to, and processed, stored and used in the United States. The data protection laws in the United States may differ from those of the country in which you are located, and your Personal Information may be subject to access requests from governments, courts, or law enforcement in the United States according to laws of the United States. By using the Site or providing us with any information, you consent to the transfer to, and processing, usage, sharing, and storage of your information, including Personal Information, in the United States as set forth in this Privacy Policy.

**9.  What Should Parents Know About Children?**

KCETLink highly recommends that parents and guardians spend time with their children when they are online or listening to or watching KCETLink content. Parents and guardians are encouraged to learn and participate in their children's online interests interactive activities, and pre-screen any information submitted by their children to any website including KCETLink Sites. We understand the importance of protecting children's privacy in the interactive world. We are a general audience Site and do not use the Site to knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13 that requires parental notice and consent under the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (" **COPPA** ") without such parental consent. If you are a child under 13 years of age, you are not permitted to use the Site and should not send any information about yourself to us through the Site.

In the event that we become aware that we have collected personal information from any child, we will dispose of that information in accordance with COPPA and other applicable laws and regulations. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information without COPPA-required consent, please contact us at [legal@kcet.org](mailto:legal@kcet.org).

**10.  What About Security?**

KCETLink offers you the convenience of making on-line membership contributions and donations via credit card. KCETLink uses commercially reasonable safeguards to keep this and other Personal Information disclosed to us secure. To reduce the risk of unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and help ensure correct usage of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. Nonetheless, KCETLink does not guarantee the security, accuracy or completeness of any such procedures. You should be aware that third parties might unlawfully intercept transmissions of Personal Information or misuse or abuse the Personal Information that we collect from you, and you use our Site and provide us with your information at your own risk.

**11.  What About Changes to the Privacy Policy?**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. If we make significant or material changes to this Privacy Policy, users will be notified through a prominently posted announcement on the homepage of the KCETLink Sites. Any changes will be effective immediately upon the posting of the revised Privacy Policy and your use of our Site indicates your consent to the privacy policy posted at the time of use. However, we will not use your previously collected Personal Information in a manner materially different than represented at the time it was collected without your consent. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy periodically to read the latest version. If you have any questions concerning this Privacy Policy, please contact us in writing as specified in above Section 7 "How Do I Change My Information and Communication Preferences?".

To the extent any provision of this Privacy Policy is found by a competent tribunal to be invalid or unenforceable, such provision shall be severed to the extent necessary for the remainder to be valid and enforceable.

//End of Privacy Policy//

The following third parties that collect information from you on our Site have given us notice that you may obtain information on their policies and practices, and in some instances opt-out of certain of their activities, as follows:

**Party** | **Service** | **For More Information** | **Use of Tracking Technologies** | **Prviacy Choices**  
---|---|---|---|---  
Google | Google Analytics for Display Advertisers, Ads Preferences Manager, and Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on | <https://support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245>   
[http://www.google.com/settings/ads](http://www.google.com/settings/ads/onweb/?hl=en&sig=ACi0TCg8VN3Fad5_pDOsAS8a4...) | Yes | <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>  
Google Adsense | Ad Serving | <http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/ads/> | Yes | <https://www.google.com/settings/ads/plugin>  
ScoreCard Research Beacon | Ad Research | <http://www.fullcirclestudies.com/about.aspx> | Yes | <http://www.fullcirclestudies.com/privacy.aspx>  
ChartBeat | Analytics | <https://chartbeat.com/privacy> | Yes | None  
AddThis | Widget | <http://www.addthis.com/about> | Yes | <http://www.addthis.com/privacy/opt-out>  
Datalogix | Advertising | <https://www.datalogix.com/privacy/> | Yes | <https://www.datalogix.com/privacy>  
DataXu | Advertising | <https://www.dataxu.com/about-us/privacy/> | Yes | <https://www.dataxu/com/about-us/privacy/data-collection-platform/>  
Facebook Connect | Widgets; Social | <https://www.facebook.com/help/privacy> | Yes | <https://www.facebook.com/help/privacy>  
Livefyre | Comments/Social | <http://legal.livefyre.com/privacy> | Yes | None  
Tapad | Advertising; Analytics | <http://www.tapad.com/consumer-privacy/> | Yes | <http://www.tapad.com/consumer-privacy/>  
  
PLEASE NOTE: We are not responsible for third-party policies or practices. We try to keep this information current, and will add to and subtract from the chart above as appropriate, but it is provided as a courtesy and may not be current or accurate. Please contact the applicable third parties regarding their privacy and data security policies and practices.
